Guide to the Scientific Research Society of Sigma Xi North America, Alpha Chapter records, 1886-1986.
Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society of North America, Alpha Chapter records, 1886-1986.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society of North America, Alpha Chapter records, 1886-1986.
37-4-194
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society of North America.Alpha Chapter.
6.4 cubic ft.
N/A
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes material pertaining to the chapter affiliations of members, 1886-1967, with correspondence, lists, forms, minutes, notices, and announcements concerning transfers, nominations, officers, committees, and branches at the Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, the Cornell Medical College in New York City, and the New York Agricultural Experiment Station in Geneva, New York; materials concerning the founding and early history of Sigma Xi, 1886-1945, including correspondence, printed material, manuscripts, and speeches; extensive financial records, 1909-1973, including correspondence, lists, reports, bills, receipts, checks, and bank statements; miscellaneous correspondence, 1930-1976; Alpha Chapter membership lists, 1949-1974; administrative information, 1887-1976, including procedural manuals, by-laws, constitutions, yearbooks, song, annual reports, programs, proceedings, minutes, correspondence, and presidential addresses; petitions for new chapters of Sigma Xi, 1909-1971, initiation announcements, and completed nomination forms, 1965-1971, with unclaimed certificates and insignia order forms; volumes, 1886-1966, include minutes, petitions for new chapters, account books, histories of Sigma Xi, and photographic negatives of the chapter signature book. Also included is a 1904 Sigma Xi diploma. Includes correspondence of Simpson Linke and Yervant Terzian.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Founded at Cornell University, Sigma Xi is an honorary scientific organization composed of undergraduates, graduate students, and faculty members. Originally called the Society of the Sigma Xi, this organization merged with the Scientific Research Society in 1974, and is currently named Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society of North America.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes material pertaining to the chapter affiliations of members, 1886-1967, with correspondence, lists, forms, minutes, notices, and announcements concerning transfers, nominations, officers, committees, and branches at the Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, the Cornell Medical College in New York City, and the New York Agricultural Experiment Station in Geneva, New York; materials concerning the founding and early history of Sigma Xi, 1886-1945, including correspondence, printed material, manuscripts, and speeches; extensive financial records, 1909-1973, including correspondence, lists, reports, bills, receipts, checks, and bank statements; miscellaneous correspondence, 1930-1976; Alpha Chapter membership lists, 1949-1974; administrative information, 1887-1976, including procedural manuals, by-laws, constitutions, yearbooks, song, annual reports, programs, proceedings, minutes, correspondence, and presidential addresses; petitions for new chapters of Sigma Xi, 1909-1971, initiation announcements, and completed nomination forms, 1965-1971, with unclaimed certificates and insignia order forms; volumes, 1886-1966, include minutes, petitions for new chapters, account books, histories of Sigma Xi, and photographic negatives of the chapter signature book. Also included is a 1904 Sigma Xi diploma. Includes correspondence of Simpson Linke and Yervant Terzian.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society of North America.; Linke, Simpson, 1917-; Terzian, Yervant.; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University.Medical College.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.
Form and Genre Terms:
Histories.; Negatives.; Scrapbooks.; Speeches.; Yearbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Affiliation Related Materials
Box 1
Series II. History
Box 2
Series III. Finances
Box 2
Series IV. Correspondence
Boxes 2-3
Series V. Membership
Boxes 3-4
Series VI. Administration
Box 4
Series VII. Petitions
Boxes 4-5
Series VIII. Nominations
Boxes 5-6
Series IX. Volumes
Box 7
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Affiliation Related Materials
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes correspondence, annotated lists
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Includes correspondence
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, v-mail
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographed correspondence, blank forms
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, lists
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, lists, invitations
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affiliation Correspondence, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Affiliates, Canvases for List of New (Members), 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Includes correspondence, typescript list
  - Transfers, Credentials received and billed, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Transfers, Credentials received and billed, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Transfers, Credentials received and billed, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Transfers: completed forms, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Membership Lists, Correspondence to Correct, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Membership Lists, Correspondence to Correct, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Invitations to join Cornell Chapter, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Includes correspondence, lists
  - Affiliates Elsewhere, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Membership Lists, 1893-1943 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Includes incomplete set; printed, typescript, and typed carbon lists
  - Yearbook Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographed correspondence
  - Yearbooks, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Includes all typescripts
  - Retired Members: correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alumni List for Affiliation program, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Includes typescript, annotated list
  - Inactive Members, Reminders - Requests for Reinstatement, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Leave Notices, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Resignations, 1917-1946 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Includes letters
  - Associate Members, Inquiries re Promotion, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, 1 completed nomination form
  - Nomination Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, nomination forms, mimeographed correspondence, lists
  - Nomination Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, nomination forms, annotated lists
  - Nomination Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, nomination forms, mimeographed correspondence, blank forms
  - Nomination Lists, 1928-1933 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Includes mimeographed lists
  - Nomination Lists, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Includes mimeographed lists, typescript press release, carbon copy of outgoing letter and list, postcards
  - Nomination Lists, 1938-1942 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Includes mimeographed lists, letter
  - Nomination Lists, 1943-1961 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Includes annotated mimeographed lists
  - Nomination Blank with suggestions for improvement, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Includes typed carbon blank, printed blank, handwritten note
  - Local Officers and Committees, Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, typescript excerpts from Sigma Xi constitution, Report of Committee on Eligibility Policy
  - Richard Bradfield, James B. Sumner, correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Includes chapter presidents - correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - John W. Wells, chapter secretary, correspondence, 1949-1955 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, lists, mimeographed correspondence
  - Election of Officers and Committees, correspondence, 1939-1950 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Lists of officers and committees, 1886-1951 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Includes typescript, typed carbon, handwritten and annotated lists
  - Banquet Committee, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, initiation programs, reply cards, mimeographed correspondence, typed carbon list of receipts, typescript/handwritten list
  - Program Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, typed carbon annotated list, mimeographed correspondence, handwritten notes, postcard
  - Program Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographed correspondence, abstract, handwritten notes, press release
  - Current Minutes, 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Includes typed carbon copies of chapter and committee meeting minutes
  - Correspondence with National Office, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, blank forms, mimeographs, postcards
  - Correspondence with National Office, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Includes carbon copies of outgoing letters, handwritten notes
  - Edward Ellery, President of Sigma Xi, Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, cellophane diploma envelope, pencilled note
  - George A. Baitsell, Executive Secretary of Sigma Xi, Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, diploma orders, mimeographs, membership list, Constitution of the United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization
  - National Convention, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, Congressional Record offprint
  - New Members, Press Release Listing by State of Origin, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Includes Cornell Chapter mimeograph
  - Geneva, NY, NYS Agricultural Experiment Station, Sigma Xi Membership, Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Geneva Sigma Xi Branch, Correspondence, 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, transfer forms, annotated lists
  - Cornell Medical College, New York City, Sigma Xi Branch, Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, annotated lists, mimeographs, handwritten notes
  - Cornell Medical College branch, correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, annotated list
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory Sigma Xi branch, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, transfer requests
  - CAL branch, 1954-1967 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Includes correspondence, annotated lists, carbon copies of outgoing letters, affiliation cards, mimeographs
  - Sigma Xi Grant-in-Aid of Research Application Blank, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Includes 2 copies
  - Sigma Xi Fellowship, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, ballots, statement of conditions
  - Notices and Announcements, 1941-1947 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Includes printed and mimeographed letters to members, some annotated, broadsides, postcards, carbon copies of outgoing letters, typescript annotated lists
  - Notices and Announcements, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Includes carbon copies of outgoing letters, annotated lists, mimeographed notices, printed program, clippings, broadside
  - Materials and Tasks for Initiation, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, diploma orders, typed carbon initiation program, mimeographs, typed annotated lists, handwritten notes and lists, postcards, blank forms
  - Unclaimed Sigma Xi diplomas, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Includes 1 diploma, 1942, with handwritten note
  - Lecturer in Residence, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Miss Barra, Alumni House, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Includes handwritten note, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Insignia Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Fields and Eligibility for Sigma Xi Membership, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, agenda for 38th annual convention, President's Report for 1937, Secretary's Report for 1937, handwritten notes, report of joint conference with National Executive Committee, Eligibility in Sigma Xi, annotated lists including "Fields of Science"
  - Membership Structure, National Committee, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, handwritten and typescript lists
- Series II. History
  - Correspondence with the Librarian, 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, typescript list, printed acknowledgements, annotated index card
  - The Organization of the Scientific Society of the Sigma Xi. F. Van Vleck, J.H. Comstock, C.D. Marx: Andrus & Church, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Printed booklet.
  - Copy of Historical Sketch, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Includes typed annotated carbon copy of "Historical Sketch" by L.F. Randolph, list of Alpha Chapter publications, typed carbon photocopy and annotated paste-ups, printed booklet - Sigma Xi History 1886-1936, Constitution and By-laws
  - Preamble to first Constitution of Sigma Xi, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes original manuscript draft
  - First Constitution of Sigma Xi, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Early Letters of Sigma Xi Founders, 1892-1915 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Includes typescript and handwritten correspondence of James McMahon, Frank Van Vleck, Elias Duran, W.A. Day
  - Unpublished Manuscripts and Letters of Professor Henry Shaler Williams (selected), 1910-1918 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes handwritten annotations, manuscript - "The Sigma Xi Idea" - with typescript copy
  - Early published notices of Sigma Xi, 1886-1912 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Includes typescript copies of newspaper notices, articles and announcements, toast card for Sigma Xi Banquet, single-sheet leaflet - "Sigma Xi: Report on Extension," typescript copy of "Sigma Xi: A Sketch on the Origin and Growth of the Society - Its Aims and Ideals" by J. McMahon, 1900, in Cornell Alumni News, printed list of officers through 1902, printed letter to members, handwritten notes and sketches, clippings
  - History, Various Memorials, 1926-1942 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, handwritten annotation, printed program for Initiation and Henry Shaler Williams memorial, printed program for Initiation and Banquet for Edward Bausch, typescript list, clippings
  - Semi-Centennial Celebration, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Semi-Centennial Celebration, Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, lists, handwritten notes
  - Semi-Centennial Printed Material, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Includes announcement, program, list of research demonstrations, clippings
  - A.R. Mann, "Acceptance of Sigma Xi Memorial by Cornell University", 1936-06-20 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Includes typed carbon copy of speech, letter
  - Notes on Early History of Sigma Xi from statements of living founders attending the Semi-Centennial, Ithaca. Transcribed by L.F. Randolph, Cornell Chapter Secretary, 1936-06-20 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Includes handwritten pages
  - Historical Sketch, Cornell Chapter, by L.F. Randolph, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Includes copy of original manuscript, and correspondence relating to the preparation of the manuscript, annotated typed carbon copy, correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Letters of living founders of Sigma Xi to officers of Cornell Chapter on the occasion of the Semi-Centennial Celebration, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Historical Exhibit, Semi-Centennial Celebration, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Typescript list of items exhibited
  - A.R. Mann, Presidential Address at Sigma Xi initiation exercises, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Includes typed and signed speech
  - Frank Van Vleck, address before Semi-Centennial Gathering. "The Inception of the Society of the Sigma Xi", 1936 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Typescript carbon copy
  - Sigma Xi Research Exposition (Cornell Chapter), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Includes mimeographs, program, 1 number of The Cornellian Council Bulletin
- Series III. Finances
  - Treasurer and Printing, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Includes carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Treasurer, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Includes carbon copies of outgoing letters, typescript annotated lists, correspondence, handwritten notes and lists, carbon copy of Financial Statement
  - Finance Committee, 1946-1951 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Includes carbon copies of Reports and Financial Statements, correspondence, typescript memoranda, mimeographs, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Treasurer, 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Includes carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, correspondence, annotated lists
  - James L. Gaylor, Sigma Xi Treasurer, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, Treasurer's Report, handwritten notes, mimeographs, annotated lists, blank forms
  - Gaylor, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, page from desk calendar mimeographs, annotated lists, chart, IRS form 1099, savings passbook, printed copy of Cornell Chapter By-Laws
  - Bill Stubs and Receipts, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Includes includes memorandum-type correspondence
  - Bill Stubs and Receipts, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bill Stubs and Receipts, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bill Stubs and Receipts, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Includes includes memorandum-type correspondence, photocopied list, handwritten notes, list of officers and committees, examination book used for notes
  - Bank Statements, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bank Statements, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bank Statements, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bank Statements, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bank Statements, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bank Statements, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bank Statements, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cancelled Checks, Bills, Statements, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Includes memorandum-type correspondence
  - Bills, Receipts, Cancelled Checks, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Includes tax forms, bank statements, memorandum-type correspondence
  - Fiscal Records, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Includes memorandum-type correspondence, minutes and reports, bills, receipts, bank statements, cancelled checks
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1909-1914 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Includes typescript and carbon copies
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1910-1938 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Includes incomplete set; handwritten note, typescript and typed carbon reports, Inventory of Club Dishes and Silverware, correspondence, mimeographs, annotated lists
  - Treasurer's Report, Vouchers Supporting, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    Includes typescript lists, bills and receipts, memorandum-type correspondence, mimeographs, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Includes typed annotated carbon copies
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1956-1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Includes annotated mimeographs, handwritten page
- Series IV. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1930-1941 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Incldues correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters
  - Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, printed invitation
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, printed slips, photocopied Sigma Xi diploma, offprint, postcards, handwritten lists
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, dues slips, envelopes
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, lists
  - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, typescript budget, mimeographs, proceedings of 1961 Annual Convention
  - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographed list and memoranda
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, dues slips, mimeographs
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, dues slips
  - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, nomination lists
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, nomination lists, other lists, Treasurer's Report, lecture announcement
  - Correspondence to Members, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Includes mimeographs, nomination lists, officer and committee lists, nomination blank, lecture notice, Treasurer's Report
  - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Include correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, dues/affiliation slips, mimeographs
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Includes correspondence, mimeographs, carbon copies of outgoing letters, membership lists
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, membership lists, mimeographs
  - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Includes correspondence, typed annotated Initiation program, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, officer and committee lists
  - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Includes correspondence, mimeographs, nomination lists, printed initiation program, carbon copies of outgoing letters, Treasurer's Report
  - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Includes carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, officer and committee lists, handwritten lists correspondence, certificate order form carbons
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Includes Sigma Xi certificates, insignia order forms, Boston College Installation programs
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    Includes correspondence, carbon copies of outgoing letters, mimeographs, bank slips
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    Includes correspondence, mimeographs, printed announcements, officer and committee lists, carbon copies of outgoing letters, handwritten notes, nomination lists, blank forms
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 67)